Ian Waddell



i.83.waddell@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ian-waddell2000



https://github.com/IWaddell01

Summary

I'm an aspiring software engineer, serious computer hardware enthusiast, and can play a mean game of Rocket League. Strong computer hardware and troubleshooting skills thanks to a decade of tinkering with anything and everything, and a full stack of software engineering skills thanks to Kenzie Academy, including Javascript, React, Python, Django, and SQL.

Experience



DoorDash

Sep 2019 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

Package Handler

FedEx

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019 (3 months)

Education

Kenzie Academy

Certification, Full-Stack Web Development 2020 - 2021

Lockport Township High School

2014 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

- Front-End Software Engineering Kenzie Academy
- Full Stack Software Engineering Certificate Kenzie Academy

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Django • React.js • Computer Maintenance • Troubleshooting • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • css • SQL

Honors & Awards

Illinois State Scholar - Illinois Student Assistance Commission Feb 2018